Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world believing.
That surely someday we
just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up way up high.
Always step up, if brains
are rubbed up to the sky.
Never give up, our wishes
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
Alright, fire!
God!
That's way too many!
No Gum-Gum!
Legs full! Boot! Now what?
No more legs!
Devil Fruit.
Ha-ha-ha!
I know just the thing for you!
Now fire! Fire!
Aim right for the bottom of their vessel.
Come on, let's turn back.
Like I would ever do that, Usopp.
Go forward!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did you not notice the nonstop gunfire?
I told you!
We're this close to
sinking to a watery calf!
Ha ha ha!
You'll never escape the wrath
of Brownbeard, you fools!
I'm the former pirate with a
bounty of over 80 million berries!
Fair enough.
But you won't forget this.
No way! He got us! We're falling!
This is bad.
Ha! That's all it, teacher.
Real nice shot there, boss.
They're dead meat now.
It serves you right.
Struggling won't help you.
Soon you'll all freeze
and think like rots.
So cold. It's over.
We're gonna be the snow cones. This blows.
This is all your fault, Luffy.
We could have got away.
But, oh, you just had to keep on
putting his butt in, didn't you?
Oh, no.
I can't even talk now.
I'm sorry. Oh, well.
I guess they won't join
the crew after all.
Now, finish them off!
Now, here's what we'll do.
You stay and keep them from drowning.
I'll get slicing.
Be right back.
Make it quick.
I don't know how, but...
It'll just take a sec.
Zoro, are you okay?
Hey!
Why are there sharks in a lake?
It's simple.
That's not a lake. It's a sea.
The battle between Akainu and Aokiji was
so explosive, it left a massive crater.
Water from the sea
poured in through cracks
in the island and made what you see here.
It brought plenty of
sea life along with it.
Ah, no, no kidding, Zoro,
also hurry, I'm cold.
Aim and fire, there's
nowhere they can go now.
Hate to say it, but he's right!
Send them straight to hell!
After all the crazy crap I've lived through,
this is the thing that's gonna kill me!
Now meet your maker!
Fire!
My soldiers.
What just happened to them?
I think I know!
Colder than a blizzard,
the wind from the underworld
cuts like an icy blade.
Damn you!
What is this?
By the way, I just froze your gun barrels,
so I would advise against shooting.
Unless you want them to explode, that is.
Who the hell are you?
And why the skeleton disguise?
My name is of no consequence. It's Brook.
Make up your mind.
I died once and became a skeleton.
And now that I live again, my second
life is devoted to the Straw Hat crew!
You can call me the Soul King.
I don't know how you froze our guns.
But... you'll pay! Pay?
And how do you plan to make me?
Bastard! That's it!
I've lost enough friends
in my time, so I say...
No way!
What the hell?
He's so fast, it's scary!
They beat up the Sharks?
What?
Where did those wretched pirates go?
Right here.
This is a pleasant surprise, Brooke!
It's so good to see you all.
Who knew running from
that terrifying ghost
would lead me directly to where you were?
Centaurs, dragons, sharks.
I don't care what this
island throws at us!
You should have run
while you had the chance,
because you sure as hell can't stop us.
But this damn weather,
that's another thing.
I can't cut that with
my sword. It's freezing.
I can barely walk.
I told you guys, don't you remember?
We can't just go to the cold
side like this, I said, but no.
Hey, look over there.
If you ask me, we got lucky.
Running into them was the best
thing that could have happened.
They're close.
Let's open fire.
Hold on.
I think I've seen them before.
Good thinking, Robin.
I called the fourth guy from the right.
Yeah, nice one.
I'll take the guy next to him.
All right, now, let me see.
The girl on the far left will do nicely.
Huh?
I'm confused.
Those coats look nice and warm.
All right, good idea.
But please get me wiped out!
Uh-oh, they're not going to
take our clothes, are they?
No way, then we'll freeze to death.
I remember now, that Straw Hat.
Yes, from two years ago.
That came from the worst generation.
There's no doubt.
That's Firefist's brother.
The pirates draw at Luffy.
With a 400 million bounty.
What?
He's gonna kill us all
Please don't hurt me!
Come on, kids.
Let's karate chop our way out.
Where's that back door?
Hold your treat.
We mustn't go.
That fellow back there was the
one that cut my body into three.
No way.
Seriously?
So, do you think he might still
have the rest of you? On hand?
I highly doubt he would. Okay,
then. It can wait. Take me back.
Perhaps I can obtain some information.
The only relevant information right now
is that we need to run the hell away.
That was the samurai.
And the Straw Hats.
I'm not letting them get away.
Room.
Hey, did you guys just see that?
The air is all perky.
All right, shambles.
whoa!
I just felt something weird!
No time to think about it right now!
Keep moving! rug rats!
The exit can't be far!
What the hell?
My cigarette go
super
close to!
busting our way out of here!
I can feel it!
Good thing!
I got these Tribe power!
Tank transit crap!
You're acting really weird!
that ability is way too powerful! Yeah!
That guy really creeps me out!
I don't think so!
None of you are going anywhere!
He turned our ship into
abstract art! It's a wreck!
We can't take that out to sea! I know!
We're stuck on this crappy
island with that lunatic!
You work for the government too, bud!
And just now, you broke
contract by causing us trouble!
Yeah, cut it out, Law!
Wait till we tell HQ!
You're gonna lose your title!
See how much I care.
Now scan.
What's that do? Oh, no!
Huh?
Transponder snails?
Wait, I lost mine!
Whoa, so did I!
Hey, you stole them, didn't you?
Give those back!
What do you need them for, huh?
I can't let you reveal what
you've seen on this island.
This way, the government
never has to hear about it.
Warlord or not, you've
pushed your luck too far now.
The abob fruit, huh?
Let's see what it's made of.
Don't let him cut you, man.
Just stay away.
He's happy!
What the?
I don't need you here.
Get outside of the circle.
Wait, what circle?
Look, as long as you're in this vicinity,
you're like a patient
on an operating table.
Law is the surgeon of death.
He can control anything within
his operating room at will.
He'll end you!
Trafalgar Law!
You've left me no choice!
Stop to see him! You can't win!
Your hockey's too weak!
No, it can't be!
Huh?
You cut her clean in
half, you sick bastard!
Hey, uh, you're still alive, right?
Say something!
Pathetic.
Flying here in pieces, cut
down but left to live in shame.
Why won't you finish me, Trafalgar?
You may wield a sword, but
don't act like you're a master.
Honor is something that
you earn, not beg for.
Weaklings like you don't get
to choose where they die.
Enough!
Your sword can't even reach me.
Don't bother.
You still want to fight?
I can chop you up some more.
Stand back!
If you lay another finger on
our captain, we'll mess you up!
Hey, captain, don't worry.
We'll see how cocky this bastard
is after we fill him with land!
What the hell?
How is he shooting at us?
I don't see any gun!
We shot him and he didn't even bunch!
You shot at yourselves,
you bunch of imbeciles.
I switched your bullets
with the falling snow.
Ha ha!
Hey, he's cheating!
That isn't fair!
Get down!
He'll take your head clean off, man!
He cut a damn ship in half!
You can't stop this guy!
He's too strong!
Get out of there, Captain!
Captain, no!
Yeah!
Captain Smokey!
You may be a warlord, but
you're still just a pirate.
That weapon you're swinging around,
it's tipped with sea prism stone.
I could feel it in an instant.
His ice sculpture!
I mean our ship is coming down!
I think that's our cue to run away!
We can't fight him anyway!
We got no business here!
You'll be okay!
There's nothing we can do!
It's our fight!
I'm telling you, we're
dead weight right now!
Weight blow!
Out of the circle!
Get out of the circle!
That noise sure was loud, huh?
I bet it was Saint.
Hey, Krakatar, you still don't want to
tell me where the rest of my crew is at?
Keep dreaming, but you're not gonna
get a word out of me, all right?
We gotta get to that big building
before someone gets hurt.
Like me?
Or my crew you robbed?
You're nothing but a bunch of thugs.
And now you gotta humiliate me like this.
Man up, man-a-dial, crack-o-man, whatever.
Brooke, you don't even have skin.
You're sitting there shivering,
but you can't be cold, right?
Did you just steal that coat
because you wanted to fit in?
What if I did?
We've been able to keep ourselves warm,
but I fear the others
might not be so fortunate.
If they get frostbite, they
could lose any number of limbs.
That's enough!
Just spare us your
gruesome concerns, okay?
What should we do, Master?
Law and Smoker are having
an Alto battle outside.
Law has made a nuisance of himself.
He was supposed to make
them leave peacefully.
Also, the pirates took the children from
the biscuit room with them to the front.
They ran into Law, but it doesn't look
like they're part of the struggle.
Wait, that means that the Navy
saw the children? Yes, sir.
That was the last thing I wanted.
They might not know what, but now
they know we're up to something.
At this point, even if we kill Smoker,
the Navy will only send more
Marines to investigate us.
I thought so.
I hope you have something helpful
to contribute to this, Monet.
I know who our intruders are.
Never mind, Smoker.
We should have kept a
tartar leash on them.
Oh, right.
I guess I neglected to tell you.
They already took out Dr.
Vegapunk's dragon, as well as
Brownbeard's centaur patrol unit.
They did what? How?
The people that you kidnapped
weren't their only crew members,
just the only crew members on the ship.
The rest had already set
off for the Burning Lands.
They've since crossed the lake.
I imagine they'll be here any minute now.
Huh?
At least we know who we're
dealing with. You see?
There's no doubting it's them, right?
The faces match.
That's true.
So long, ship.
There's no fixing that.
Got your legs back yet?
You're not in any pain now, are you?
Hey, you got a foot on
your wrist there, pal.
You're gonna want to take care of that.
Huh?
Oh, geez, you're right.
I don't even know who
this foot belongs to.
Damn it!
We can't even contact HQ anymore!
We're stranded on this
crappy island! Law's a jerk!
I thought the warlords were on our side!
There's one thing you always
need to remember, Toshiki.
A pirate's a pirate.
No matter where they
go, they never change.
All warlords are the same. He was right.
This plan must be why you joined up
with the seven warlords, isn't it?
But what the hell are you after?
I don't know.
I've never been a fan
of the Warlord system.
Pirates can't be trusted
no matter who they are.
You got that one right.
There's something big going on here.
And you're only part of it—who is it?
Who's running this show? First.
First
What's your story?
What are you doing here?
If you want to get to
the bottom of something,
then you've got to broaden your
horizons, or you'll miss the truth.
Scalpel.
My heart.
You can beg, but I don't have
to tell you a damn thing.
Thank you.